(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T02:13:49.721800",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey everybody
Today I would like to introduce you
To the one and only entertainer
始まった show time 鳴り響く歓声
The show time has started, cheers are ringing out
おジャンガジャンガ 心踊らせ
Oh janga janga, let your heart dance
指を鳴らせば 変わる景色が
Snap your fingers and the scenery changes
退屈な街でも ほら ブロードウェイ 今宵の主役は 私よ
Even in a boring city, look, Broadway! I'm tonight's protagonist!
1, 2 let's go 3, 4
It's my showtime
Let the show begin 最高のショー 楽しみましょう！！
Let the show begin, the best show, let's enjoy it!!
一度きりの人生なのだから ダーリンダーリンダーリンダーリン yeah
Because you only live once, darling darling darling darling yeah
恋も仕事も いざ 東雲よ
Love and work, now until dawn!
1, 2, 3, 4 hah!! Let the show begin
照らす moon light スポットライトにして
The illuminating moonlight, make it a spotlight
おラタタッタッ 軽快な ステップで
With a light-footed rata-tatta step
音を鳴らせば 拍手の渦が 轟く スタンディングオベーション
Make a sound and a whirlpool of applause roars in a standing ovation
今宵の主役に 貴方も
You too are tonight's protagonist!
1, 2 let's go 3, 4
It's our showtime
Let the show begin 最高のショー 楽しみましょう！！
Let the show begin, the best show, let's enjoy it!!
一度きりの人生なのだから ダーリンダーリンダーリンダーリン yeah
Because you only live once, darling darling darling darling yeah
恋も仕事も いざ 東雲よ
Love and work, now until dawn!
1, 2, 3, 4 hah!! Let the show begin
Do it naughty everybody come follow me
Yeah
Be scandalous 今にも
Be scandalous, even now
Let's do it very very very bad
So beautiful 何度でも
So beautiful, no matter how many times
Let's do it very very very bad
So beautiful
何度でも
No matter how many times,
Let's away very very very very
冴えないあなたも燃え尽きましょう
Let's burn out, even dull old you.
一瞬だけの人生でしょ
It's a life of just a fleeting moment.
ダーリン ダーリン 踊り明かそう
Darling, darling, let's dance the night away.
欲しいものも出尽した脳みそ
A brain where even desires have run out.
One, two, three, four, huh!
Let's show begin
Let the show begin.
冴えない最後のショー 愉しみましょう
Let's enjoy this dull final show.
一瞬だけの人生なんだ
It's a life of just a fleeting moment.
ダーリン ダーリン 踊り明かそう
Darling, darling, let's dance the night away.
欲しいものも出尽した脳みそ
A brain where even desires have run out.
One, two, three, four, huh!
This is my show time
This is my showtime.
I'm breaking out 冴えないほかの誰でもないの me
I'm breaking out, not anyone else, just me.
君の願いも簡単に叶えたから抜け出す me
Escaping now that I've easily granted your wish.
満たされない 欲に囚われ
Trapped in unfulfilled desires,
俗だらけの世界とは break up
breaking up with this vulgar world.
I wish no filter ありのままで怖くない future
I wish no filter, a future not afraid of being raw.
見栄も我慢もありのまま Adoniram
Vanity and patience, just as they are, Adoniram.
満たされない 間違いはない Adoniram
Unfulfilled, with no mistakes, Adoniram.
拘る my style 行き所のない
Clinging to my style, with nowhere to go,
声吐く my guideline なにひとつ my life 見せるだけ 振り向かない愛
exhaling my guideline, my life in every way, just showing love that won't look back.
自信満々のレクチャーリー
A super confident lecture.
見捨てないで捨てないで だけどマイウォー
Don't abandon me, don't throw me away, but my war.
見せつけるエクスタシー
Flaunting ecstasy.
溺れplay 愛おけだから 轟く my way
Drowning in play, because it's love OK, roaring my way.
見せろよ that a future
Show me that future.
Be naked Be naked Be naked
全て望むままに get
get everything just as desired.
Be naked Be naked Be naked
全て望むままに get
get everything just as desired.
Show me what that a future to understand
Show me what that future is to understand.
リボン無し 満もステージ 全て望むままに get
No ribbon, a full stage, get everything just as desired.
脳にもルーズ ミニマムが正義
Loose on the brain too, minimum is justice.
リボンのエイジ あの日チェインだから遠慮はしない 違いね反応
Ribbon's age, chains of that day, so no holding back, a distinct reaction.
走りがランボー 惑わせるファンタジー
Wild running, a bewitching fantasy.
見捨てたり馬鹿な差れはしないの
I won't abandon you or do anything foolish.
幕を上げるバイナリー
Raising the curtain on binary.
愛おけ 愛もけだから 飛び出せ
Love OK, because it's love too, so jump out!
Show me what that a future Be naked
Show me what that future is, be naked.
Be naked Be naked Be naked
全て望むままに get
get everything just as desired.
Be naked Be naked Be naked
全て望むままに get
get everything just as desired.
Show me what that a future
Show me what that future is.
自分隠すのは楽だよね
Hiding your true self is easy, right?
周りに合わせ手ればそれで
Just blending in with those around you,
辿り合えず一人にならずに進むから辛いの
and moving forward without missing each other or ending up alone hurts so much.
いや本当はもう気づいて 周りは狭間に濁いてる
No, actually you've already noticed, the surroundings are murky in the gaps.
なのになんで諦めてる もう一度確かめ
Then why are you giving up? Check it once more.
初めましょう リアルなショー どこからでも好きにどうぞ
Let's begin the real show, however you like from anywhere.
愛のに本当にショウ見せろ that a future
Really show love, show me that future.
Hey what you want ? 10p zombie shine
Hey, what you want? 10P zombie shine.
Hey what you need ? 大丈夫さ
Hey, what you need? It's gonna be alright.
Hey what you want ? 10p zombie shine
Hey, what you want? 10P zombie shine.
そのままで蹴り落せ いつも
Kick it down just as it is, always.
Hey what you want ? 10p zombie shine
Hey, what you want? 10P zombie shine.
Hey what you need ? 大丈夫さ
Hey, what you need? It's gonna be alright.
Hey what you want ? 10p zombie shine
Hey, what you want? 10P zombie shine.
そのままで蹴り落せ いつも
Kick it down just as it is, always.
「許されない」って 私が一番でしょ
"You won't forgive me," right? I'm number one, aren't I?
ゾッとした表情が 可愛いね 君のその身体が欲しいの
That shivering expression is cute, isn't it? I want that body of yours.
Love it? ナニにラリって
Love it? What are you hooked on?
愛 high 可哀想ね 君は悪い子なの
Love, high, how pitiful, you're a bad kid.
どの娘がお好きで? 散々に 色目がお上手で 頭脳沸き
Which girl do you like? You're looking around, flirting with everyone.
君に踊らされちゃって アタシは狂う
You make me dance, and I'm going crazy.
"What is love it?" (フフフ)
"What is love it?" (fufu)
君の血肉まで 骨の髄まで しゃぶりつくせばもう 空っぽのパペット
Down to your flesh and blood, down to your marrow, if I drain you dry, you'll be an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest is tight, isn't it? You can't breathe, can you?
それが恋と教えてあげる アハハ
I'll teach you that this is love, ahaha.
虚ろな声でほら 囁いて いい子ね 頚輪付けた君は love it
Whisper it in a hollow voice, look, good kid, you with the collar, you love it.
イカれちゃったのね 恋は盲目ね したいよね してあげるわ 逝って? アハハ
Are you crazy? No, love is blind, you want to, don't you? I'll do it for you, pass away? Ahaha.
濡れて 君の赤い生贄 溺れるまで
Until you drown in your own red fluids,
痛い痛い痛いノトンドユケ 死んで謝罪するまで 愚かか愚かか間抜けな顔して 君は悪い子なの
Ouch, ouch, fly away, until you die and apologize, how foolish, how foolish, with that stupid face, you're a bad kid.
痛いのがお好きで? 産に惨に あら お口はチャックで 何? 何?
Do you like the pain? Miserable, miserable, oh, your mouth is zipped, what? What?
性に踊らされてしまう君を噛む "What is love it?" (フフフ)
I'll eat you while you're dancing to the sex, "What is love it?" (fufu)
君の血肉まで 骨の髄まで
Down to your flesh and blood, down to your marrow,
しゃぶりつくせばもう 空っぽのパペット
if I drain you dry, you'll be an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest is tight, isn't it? You can't breathe, can you?
それが恋と教えてあげる アハハ
I'll teach you that this is love, ahaha.
濡れて 君の赤い生贄 溺れるまで 痛い痛い痛いノトンドユケ 息が止まるまで
Until you drown in your own red fluids, ouch, ouch, fly away, until you die and apologize.
愚かか愚かか間抜けな顔して 君は悪い子なの
How foolish, how foolish, with that stupid face, you're a bad kid.
痛いのがお好きで? 惨に惨に あら お口はチャックで 何? 何?
Do you like the pain? Miserable, miserable, oh, your mouth is zipped, what? What?
性に踊らされてしまう君を噛む "What is love it?" (フフフ)
I'll eat you while you're dancing to the sex, "What is love it?" (fufu)
君はピエロね 愛を囁いて 人間の形した君は love it
You're a clown, whispering love, you, in the shape of a human, love it.
イカれちゃったのね 恋は盲目ね したいよね してあげるわ 逝って? アハハ
Are you crazy? No, love is blind, you want to, don't you? I'll do it for you, pass away? Ahaha.
報イインエ 汚レタ血ニ溺レレルマデ イタイイタイイタイノトンドユケ 息ガ止マルマデ
Until you drown in your own red fluids, ouch, ouch, fly away, until you die and apologize.
皆さん! 本日は...
Hello everyone, today is...
伊咲リオナ生誕祭2026に 遊びに来てくれて 本当にありがとうございます!
Isaki Riona's Birthday Festival 2026, thank you so much for coming to hang out with me!
別々賞罰! えーっとね、きっと、ラブイット! 3曲続けてお披露させていただきました! どうですか?
I was able to deliver three consecutive songs: "Betther Shocking," "Habitual," and "Loveit?" How was it?
改めて自己紹介をさせてください!
Let me introduce myself again.
私の元に合図ね! リオナインダステージ! フラグラのリーダー 伊咲リオナです! プラプラ! よろしくお願いします!
I am Isaki Riona, the leader of Fragrance! Pleased to meet you!
はぁ、息切れが... 息切れしちゃうんですけど、はぁ、今日のですね、ハッシュタグはっきり...
I'm out of breath, I'm out of breath, but today, hashtag is #IsakiRiona...
伊咲リオナ生誕祭2026です!
...Isaki Riona Birthday Festival 2026!
たくさん、たくさん つぶやいてください! 私、絶対見に行くのでね、みんなが感想とかを送ってくれるの、すごく楽しみにしています!
Please tweet a lot, a lot! I will definitely go read them, so I'm really looking forward to seeing everyone's thoughts and comments!
そしてですね、本日、ライブパフォーマンスをさせていただくステージは、こちらです! どうですか?
And today, the stage where I get to perform live is right here! How do you like it?
ショーみたいでさ、めっちゃ良くない?
It's like a show, right? Isn't it super cool?
あとね、伊咲リオナっていうね、名前がたくさん刻まれていたり、ハートの風船だったり、王冠だったり、いろんな装飾があって、とってもキラキラしてます!
Also, you can see names like "Isaki Riona" engraved everywhere, heart-shaped balloons, and crowns—it has all sorts of decorations and looks super sparkly!
ここでね、踊れることが今日すごく、すごく、幸せです! ありがとうございます!
I'm so, so happy that I get to dance here today. Thank you so much!
そして、本日のライブのタイトルが「ジ・ワンド・オンリー」となっております。こちらの意味は、唯一無二という意味です。
And today's live title is "Jiwand Only." This means "uniquely and only."
このタイトルに恥じないように、全力で、全力でパフォーマンスしていくので、どうかこの時間があなたの心に、何か届けられる、そんな時間になれるように、今日は頑張りたいと思います!
To make sure this title isn't for nothing, I'm going to perform with all my might, so I hope this time can somehow reach your hearts. Today, I'll do my best!
それでは、次はお待ちかねのゲストパートです! どうぞ!
Now, next is our much-anticipated guest part! Here you go!
Blah Blah Blah Blah
I'm a B
てかてかノーモラルな混沌 触ればかわいいの琴線
Even if you're playful and teasing, it's cute.
高天原からほら
Soaring high from Takamagahara, look.
Hi, そう、面がエラーでも 面がキュートなら 面キラ だとか貼られたレッテル
Hey, so even if you're a clown and they call you a crybaby,
行ってるメンタルは
going crazy with that mental,
さあ、よ、Smileで 転がしてく Phantom
let's roll with it with the best smile.
ごまかしてる調子少な さぁ枯れたらバイバイ アンテナ
If you're having trouble maintaining your composure, then bye-bye, antenna!
I'm a B, I'm a B, I'm always on hour, I'm a B, I'm a diva 見栄張らわやよ
I'm a B, I'm a B, I'm always on hour, I'm a B, I'm a diva with an attitude.
夢見てる少女人 夢見てる少女へ
You're looking at a crybaby, looking at a girl,
Vida, La Vida は 甘々甘々甘々の
La Vida, La Vida, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, no...
衝撃ガリガリガリ妄想 終わりなきワールド
It's a bitter-sweet illusion, break it down!
チェス盤 誰よりも客寄せるパンダ
Checkmate, drawing in crowds more than anyone, a panda,
我らはんだ まれで産んだ 自己愛性勝者
we're pandas, born like a narcissistic victor.
I'm a V, I'm a Diva
I'm a b*tch, I'm a G, I'm a live wire, I'm a b*tch, I'm a G
艶やかに空振りに終わりそうならミー お前もヘルモンスター So Love Me
glamorous, if it looks like a miss, you're a hell monster too, So Love Me.
おでまですヘルモンスター
Here comes the hell monster!
You're safe now, bruh, bruh, 免れられたら墓場までラブだ
You're safe now, bruh, bruh, if you escape, it's love till the grave,
ああ ベータのロールあった 心の中
ah, beta's rolled-up heart inside,
コスモス Like a ブッダ
Cosmos like Buddha.
キャッチーにしたいならほら 縁ならキャッチーでハイピース
If you want to make it catchy, hey, if there's a tie, catch me for high peace,
召し上がる死神 墓場から無いが
reaper feasting, from the grave, nothing's there,
我ら心叫ぶ一つもライバー
we shout our hearts out, every single one's a lifer.
生きる姿と魂を今
Turn your living form and soul
二つにして愛をバラバラに
into two now, scattering love apart,
生まれた時の喜びはボショーに
the joy of the time you were born is resting in peace,
さよならでいいな
goodbye is fine,
ダメね
too bad.
Wacha Wacha, Mecha Mecha? 落下な6日目
Wacha Wacha, Mecha Mecha? Falling on the 6th day,
あららこう感で共感ね ゲッタイな招待ね
oh my, sympathizing with feelings, getting a solid invitation,
Wacha Wacha, Mecha Mecha? 落下な6日目
Wacha Wacha, Mecha Mecha? Falling on the 6th day,
あららこう感で共感ね ゲッタイな招待ね
oh my, sympathizing with feelings, getting a solid invitation,
Wacha Wacha, Mecha Mecha? 落下な6日目
Wacha Wacha, Mecha Mecha? Falling on the 6th day,
一巻の終わりだね
It's the end of volume one.
I'm a Diva, I'm a Diva
I'm a V, I'm a Diva, I'm a wow-wow, Yo, I'm a V, I'm a Diva, La Vida I am Diva
乱れ乱れはイヤよ
disordered, disordered is no good,
夢見てる少年 夢見てる少女へ
dreaming boy, dreaming girl,
Be a Diva, La Vida, I am Diva, Amah, Amah, Amah, Amah, No!
富豪さ 子供の頃言われとろんだった
Being rich, being told so since childhood,
あのヒーローショーの人形の背中にはチャックは付いてないから開くな
that hero show doll's back has no zipper, so don't open it!
バーチャルだ ヒューマンだ
Virtual, human,
私のこの世が 存在をわわんだ
my world shouted out existence,
枯れても凌いでもバラバラな
withered or endured, scattering apart,
惚れたら死ぬぞ
If you fall in love, you'll die!
I'm a V
せんぱい、来てくれてありがとうございます! ありがとうございましたー!
Senpai, thank you so much for coming! Thank you very much!
一緒にに出られて嬉しかったですね!
I'm so happy we could perform together!
めっちゃ楽しかった! そらりお
It was so much fun! SoraRio
そらりおは永遠に不滅だよー!
SoraRio is eternal and immortal!
Ha-woo
Checkmate, I'm a superstar
Stay insane, but you rock with it, eh
Yeah, like 24/7, I'm a hot mess ya, love-hate
Get less boring, oh, my god
ホームラン、バタバタ swing my shot, ah
Whoop-whoop, uh, yeah, like a villainous, villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者 も 悪役 も 変わらない (woo)
Heroes and villains don't change (woo)
派手 に ブチ かま そう (bay a-ya-ya)
Let's smash it up flashy (bay a-ya-ya)
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
"Chaotic good" is peak right now, I can show ya how (bay a-ya-ya)
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
No way, no way, yeah, way, yeah, way, yeah
"Good versus evil" is so overdone (done)
Let's all kick back and party
Just leave it to moi (whoops)
Wah-ah
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
Uh, that's karma
Ta-da-ha-ha-ha (ah-whoops)
Wah-ah
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some-ish, get it
Yeah, that's karma
Ta-da-ha-ha-ha
Sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why're you running? (ooh-ooh)
Bet ya think you're clever (woo; bay a-ya-ya)
Whatever (bay a-ya-ya)
Run, ta-ta-talk about a "kumbaya" (bay a-ya-ya)
(Hey-yo) hey-yo, check in' this out
フルボックン ボッ ちゃって
欲望 召し上がれ
アイ dollar ハート, get down, ウィンク
"see よ なら" サイコ ですわ
(boom-boom) ドメスティック
(boom-boom) Domestic
(boom-boom) ドラマティック
(boom-boom) Dramatic
愛しき 人々
Beloved people
この指とまれ
Gather at this finger
Ay, yeah, ah, ah
ハード に ハート は ハイ に なって
Hearts get high on hard beats
弾け て 恥ずかし が 捨て ちゃえ
Bursting out, throw away your shyness
叫び 踊り 誇れ 激動 的 show 体
Shout, dance, boast, a dynamic show body
酔いしれ て ちょーだ い (heh)
Get intoxicated, it's a bit too much (heh)
道化 の パラダイス (パラダイス, ha)
Paradox of dogma (paradox, ha)
惹かれ 合う
Attracting each other
感覚 が 共鳴 共鳴
Sensations resonate and echo
"Good versus evil, but i'm which one?"
Just stuck here in the middle
That's not any fun
Wah-ah
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
Uh, that's karma
Ta-da-ha-ha-ha (ah-whoops)
Wah-ah
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some-ish, get it
Yeah, that's karma
yeah, that's karma, yeah, get down
checkmate, i'm a superstar
stay insane, but you rock with it, yeah
like 24/7, i'm a hot mess, ya love-hate
get less boring, oh my god!
swing my shot, ooh, ooh, ah, yeah
like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains are no different,
派手にブチかまそう
let's go out with a bang!
想像から創造 衝動から猛攻
From imagination to creation, from impulse to fierce attack,
ほらあっという間に 華麗に変身 変幻自在
look, in the blink of an eye, brilliantly transforming and shape-shifting.
毒々しい本能
Poisonous instinct.
ba-ya-ya-ya
sorry, i'm just better
sorry, we're go-getters
ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky
why you running?
bet' cha think you're clever
whatever!
ha, talk about a "kumbaya"
isekai queen
switch チューニング マイナー
switch tuning minor
カラフル に cacophony
colorful cacophony
歪 で 優雅 に
skewed yet elegant
welcome to miss fortune's game
ba-ya-ya-ya
カリオペ先輩来てくれてありがとうございます！
Senpai Calliope, thank you so much for coming!
イェーイ！楽しかった！またライブしよう！
Yay! That was fun! Let's do another live stream!
はい！またライブしましょう！また歌いましょう！
Yeah! Let's do another live, let's sing again!
カルテNo.2222
[Title: Karte No. 2222]
はあ…♡
Haa...♡
2-2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2-2 (doomdoomdoomdoom)
2-2-2-2 (zoomzoomzoomzoom)
2-2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2-2 (burnburnburnburn)
chuchuchu, open your karte♡
救急不可能(darling)
Impossible to rescue (Darling)
恋の病なのは(dirty)
It's a love sickness (Dirty)
どんどん熱を上げていくvirus(loveme)
The virus keeps heating up (Love me)
危険な治療(まほう)(twinkle)
Dangerous treatment (Magic) (Twinkle)
試してみる？(blink)
Want to try it? (Blink)
飽きるまで天使の優等生(heaveninhell)
An angelic honor student until you get bored (Heaven in hell)
ドキドキ動機は純粋甘い
Doki-doki, the motive is pure and sweet
曖昧乙女心どっちどっち
An ambiguous maiden heart, which one, which one?
さあ手の平の迷宮へようこそ 「いい子だね♡」
Welcome to the labyrinth in my palm, "You're a good child♡"
カルテNo.2222 運命の
Karte No. 2222 of fate,
鳴りやまないサイレン音が
the siren that won't stop ringing.
weewoowoowoo
好き？好き？高まる愛の心電図
Are you sure? The rapidly accelerating heart rate of love
はいお薬をどうぞ♡ tototou♡
Yes, here is your medicine♡ To-to-too♡
2-2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2-2 (doomdoomdoomdoom)
2-2-2-2 (zoomzoomzoomzoom)
2-2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2-2 (burnburnburnburn)
chuchuchu, open your karte♡
二十四時間(during)
24 hours (During)
呼吸困難(dizzy)
Breathing difficulty (Dizzy)
真っ赤な薔薇のトゲにキスして(kissme)
Kiss the thorns of the crimson rose (Kiss me)
麻痺みたいな台詞(drinking)
Lines like anesthesia (Drinking)
魔性のbabyface(labyrinth)
Demonic baby face (Labyrinth)
籠で飛び交う青い鳥(try&error)
The blue bird flying in the cage (Try & error)
ドクドク毒みたいな支配
Dok-dok, domination like a poison
笑顔に落下寸前チクタク
On the verge of falling into a smile, tick-tock
もう時間がない秘密の正体 「悪いこかも♡」
No more time, the secret identity, "Maybe I'm a bad child♡"
カルテNo.2222 運命の
Karte No. 2222 of fate,
追い付けない超スピードで
with super speed you can't catch up to,
weewoowoowoo
好き？好き？乱れる愛の心電図
Are you sure? The disordered electrocardiogram of love
もう重症みたいです… to-to-too me♡
It seems it's already a critical condition... To-to-too me♡
先生、緊急事態です！
Teacher, it's an emergency!
「カルテNo.2222の患者様です！」
"It's the patient of Karte No. 2222!"
「見てください！心電図がハートの形になっています！」
"Look! The electrocardiogram has turned into a heart!"
「もしもーし、聞こえますか？」
"Hello? Can you hear me?"
「どこか痛いところはありますか？」
"Is there anywhere that hurts?"
「えっ？可愛すぎて胸が苦しい？息ができない！？」
"Eh? My chest hurts because you're too cute? I can't breathe!?"
「もっと好きになっちゃうお注射しましょうね」
"Let's give you an injection so you'll like it more."
「大丈夫ですよ、ずっと私が手を握っていますからね」
"It's okay, I've been holding your hand the whole time."
「心拍数がどんどん上がっています！」
"Your heart rate is rising rapidly!"
「わっ！大変です！気を失い出しちゃったみたいです」
"Oh no! It looks like you've fainted!"
「私の声聞こえますかー？」
"Can you hear my voice?"
「好きなところ言えますかー？」
"Can you tell me what you like?"
「もうこうなったらあの手しかない！」
"Since it's come to this, there's only one way!"
「みんな離れて！いっちー！」
"Everyone stand back!"
「あーあ、だから言ったのに♡」
"Ah-ah, that's why I told you...♡"
カルテNo. さあ選んで 4Card
Karte No. Now choose 4 Card
裏表ツインテールのJoker
The twin-tailed Joker of heads or tails
Time over
そう神様さえ言う通り You're falling
Just as God says, you're falling
Take higher
ぎゅっと結んだリボン
A tightly tied ribbon,
誓いましょう Ding-dong
let's make a vow, Ding-dong
運命の警告が連なる暗示
the continuous omens of fate's warning
"2" "2" "2"
カルテNo.2222 運命の
Karte No. 2222 of fate,
鳴りやまないサイレン音が
the siren that won't stop ringing.
weewoowoowoo
好き？好き？高まる愛の心電図
Are you sure? The rapidly accelerating heart rate of love
はいお薬をどうぞ♡ tototou♡
Yes, here is your medicine♡ To-to-too♡
2-2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2-2 (doomdoomdoomdoom)
2-2-2-2 (zoomzoomzoomzoom)
2-2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2-2 (burnburnburnburn)
chuchuchu, open your karte♡
見上げたあの夜空に浮かぶ星たち
Looking up at the stars floating in that night sky
ふっと君の声が
Suddenly, your voice...
あの頃輝いてたかな
...used to shine back then, didn't it?
今になっては
Now, looking back,
ずっと分からないまま
I still don't understand.
あの時君がついた嘘
The lie you told back then
問い正さずに泣いたあの坂道
I cried on that slope without questioning it.
この先君と会えないの
From now on, I won't be able to see you,
離れ離れに身を任せてた
Leaving myself to drift apart.
いつもの後悔が風に消えてく
My usual regrets fade away in the wind.
誰にも見せないその姿を
That side of you that you showed to no one else
もうちょっとだけ見てたかったんだ
I wanted to see just a little bit longer.
時がそっと翳っている
Time is gently dimming.
その手と手繋いで笑い合った声
Holding hands, our laughing voices...
忘れはしないよ
I'll never forget them.
こんなにも流した涙も語る声もオーケストラ
All the tears I shed, and the voices speaking—an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよねさよならの声
The voice of goodbye eventually came.
忘れはしないよ
I'll never forget.
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
We should have been so close,
今では繋がりなんて
But now, any connection...
あの空だけ
...is only that sky.
馬鹿らしくなって
It became so absurd,
投げた午前3時
Tossed away at 3:00 AM.
この先君と何年も
From now on, however many years with you,
時の流れに身を任せても
Even if I surrender to the passage of time,
いつものジョークが街に消えてく
My usual jokes fade away into the city.
誰にも見せない僕の姿を
A side of myself I never show to anyone
もうちょっとだけ見せたかったんだ
I wanted to show just a little bit more.
時がそっと見乱んでる
Time is gently falling into disarray.
この目と目合わせてはっきりしたい
Meeting your eyes with mine, I want to make things clear.
もうできないかな
Is that no longer possible?
こんなにもどかしくて辛いのが
Frustrations and pain
音を立てるオーケストラ
Make a sound—an orchestra.
どこで何をしているの
Where and what are you doing?
分からないのは僕のせいなんだね
Not knowing is all my fault, isn't it?
永遠にこんな日が来るなんて
Never imagining there would ever be days like this forever,
神様イタズラなら呪いたいぐらい
If you're toying with me, God, I almost want to curse you.
その手と手繋いで笑い合った声
Holding hands, our laughing voices...
忘れはしないよ
I'll never forget them.
こんなにも流した涙も語る声もオーケストラ
All the tears I shed, and the voices speaking—an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよねさよならの声
The voice of goodbye eventually came.
忘れはしないよ
I'll never forget.
見上げたあの夜空に 浮かぶ星達
Looking up at the floating stars in that night sky,
ふと君の声が
Suddenly your voice
あの頃輝いていたかな?
was shining back then, wasn't it?
今になっては
Now,
ずっと分からないまま
I still don't understand at all.
あの時君がついた嘘
The lie you told back then
問い詰だせずに
without questioning you,
泣いたあの坂道
that slope where I cried.
この先
Beyond this point,
君と会えないの
I can't meet you anymore.
離れ離れに身を任せていた
Letting myself drift apart,
いつもの後悔が風に消えていく
The usual regrets fade away in the wind.
誰にも見せないその姿を
That figure I show to no one—
もうちょっとだけ見てたかったんだ
I wanted to see just a little more.
時がそっと佇んでいる
Time is quietly standing still.
その手と手繋いで笑い合った声
The voices that laughed hand in hand—
忘れはしないよ
I will never forget them.
こんなにも流してた涙も
Even the tears I shed so much,
語る声もオーケストラ
and the voices speaking, are an orchestra.
リオナ、お誕生日おめでとう！ありがとう！
Riona, happy birthday! Thank you!
なんと、FGのみんなが来てくれました！ありがとう！
Everyone in FG came to see us! Thank you!
よかった！やったー！おめでとう！ありがとう！
Yay! Congratulations! Thank you!
いや、ついにね、初めての生誕ライブで、そしてFGでね、こうやってライブできてすごく嬉しいよ。来てくれてありがとう！
Finally, our first birthday live, and with FG, doing a live like this makes me so happy. Thank you for coming!
え、よかったね？え、よかった？めっちゃ本当？
Huh, was it good? Huh, was it good? Really? Seriously?
え、どう、どうですか？えもかったですか？
Huh, how is it? Was it emotional?
いや、ちょっと、リオナちゃん、ちょっと、え、なんかちょっと待って、感動っていうか、泣いちゃうよ。
Well, wait a minute, Riona-chan, wait, it's so emotional, I'm gonna cry.
え、ちょっと待って！泣いちゃうかと思った。みんなってこうやってね、みんなの誕生日ライブがあるかどうかわかんないんだけど。
Wait a minute! I thought I'd cry. Wondering if everyone will have a birthday live like this...
いや、どうだろうな。でも、リオナだけあってニコチ達ないの？
Well, I wonder. But wait, does only Riona have Niconichi?
え、待って、私たちもさせてよ！どういうこと！？
Wait, let us do it too! What do you mean?!
リーダー出させてくれてありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you for letting our leader perform! Thank you!
リーダーさしてもらって、ありがとうございます！今日は、お誕生日プレゼントにみんなからの超絶可愛い…
Thank you for letting us be leaders! Today, for your birthday present, we want super cute...
「リオナおめでとう」っていうプレゼントが欲しいんだけど、いいかな？
"Congratulations, Riona" as a birthday present, is that okay?
いやです！いやです！いやです！お誕生日だからさ、ありがとうって言って！
No way! No way! No way! It's your birthday, so say thank you!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Thank you!
もらっていいですか、プレゼント？じゃあ、おねだりしよう！
Can I have the present? Then let's beg for it!
「あみて、あみて」みたいなやつ。え、じゃあ「せーの」って言うから「リオナおめでとう」って言ってね？
Like "Look at me, look at me." Okay, I'll say "Ready, go" so say "Congratulations, Riona"!
わかった。オッケー。プレゼントね、プレゼント。
Understood. Okay. Present, right, present.
まあ、プレゼントならしゃーないな。ちゃんと可愛くやってやよ。ちゃんとかわいいんだからね！可愛いね、そうだよ。ちゃんとかわいいんだよ。
Well, if it's a present, can't be helped. Do it cutely. Because you're cute! You're cute, that's right. You're really cute.
まあ、まかせなって。可愛いね。オッケー、オッケー。
Well, leave it to me. Cute. Okay, okay.
せーの！
Ready, go!
リオナ！
Riona!
おめでとう！ちょっと、でもちょっと待って！見本見せてよ。
Congratulations! Wait a minute! Show us an example first.
見本見せてよ！ちょっと、ちょっと。初めての生誕だもん！
Show us an example! Wait, wait. It's our first birthday!
「そうそう」にね、愛の言葉みたいなの。あわわわ。愛がいいよね？愛がいい！
Like words of love. Awa-wa-wa. Love is good, right? Love is good!
愛の言葉。ね、お姉ちゃん。セクシーで可愛いくて愛。セクシー。可愛い。愛。じゃあ、全身で！
Words of love. Hey, big sis. Sexy and cute and love. Sexy. Cute. Love. Okay, with your whole body!
できますよ、リオナのね、リオナさんの言葉まで。
We can do it, right up to Riona's own words.
3、2、1、はい！
Three, two, one, go!
今年も、来年も、さ来年も、あなたに祝ってもらえますように！に！おめでとー！
I hope you'll celebrate with me this year, next year, and the year after that! Happy birthday!
おめでとー！ありがとー！あなたはまだおいのこりです。
Happy birthday! Thank you! You're still lingering around.
まるでこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
It seemed to me that we are the only people in this world,
なんて少しだけ夢をみてしまっただけ
so for a moment I just dreamed a little dream.
つま先に月明かり 花束の香り 指に触れる指
Moonlight on my toes, the scent of a bouquet of flowers, a finger touching my finger.
さよならもう行かなくちゃ 何もかも忘れて
Goodbye, I must go now, forgetting everything.
硝子の上を裸足のまま歩く
I'm walking barefoot on the glass,
痛むごとに血が流れて落ちていく
and with each painful step, drops of blood drip from my feet.
お願いその赤い足跡を辿って会いにきて
I beg you, follow these red footprints and come to me.
ガラスの上を
On the glass...
裸足のまま歩く 痛むごとに
walking barefoot, with each pain,
血が流れて落ちていく お願いその
blood flows and falls, I beg you,
赤い足跡を辿って 会いにきて
follow those red footprints and come to me.
錆びたプールに離れていく金魚
A goldfish released into a rusty pool,
靴箱の中隠したリンゴ
an apple hidden in a shoe cabinet,
萎びた君の肌に残る傷跡は遠い
scars left on your withered skin are far away.
君の想いは 泳いだ迷子
Your feelings are a swimming lost child.
どこにいるの ここにいるよ
"Where are you?" "I'm right here."
何をしても ずっと見てるよ
No matter what you do, I'll always be watching.
今夜 街が違ってみえたそう
Tonight, the city seemed different.
そばにいてよ 遊びに行こうよ
Stay by my side, let's go play.
どこで見ているの
Where are you looking?
ガラスの上を 立ち止まらず歩く 痛むことに 血が流れて 落ちていく
Walking across the glass without stopping, as pain causes blood to flow and fall.
お願い その若い足跡をたどって
Please, follow those youthful footprints...
会いに来て
...and come meet me.
輪郭 この世界で
In the outline of this world,
二人だけ 見つめ合っていたね
the two of us were just gazing at each other.
なんて 少しだけ 夢を見てしまっただけ
Oh, how I just dreamed a little dream...
なんて だから うわぁ...
Oh... so, wow...
頬を刺す 朝の山手通り
Yamate street in the morning stings my cheeks
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty box of cigarettes
今日もまた 足の踏み場はない
Today again I have no space even for my feet
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
And my small room pampers my loneliness
「不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love my unsettled screams,
未来等見ないで
don't look to the future,
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
live only in the present you can be confident in.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name right,
身体を触って
touch my body;
必要なのは是だけ認めて」
acknowledge that this is the only thing you need."
愛している 独り泣き喚いて
I love you. I'm bawling alone,
夜道を弄れど虚しい
and I wander about the streets at night, but I feel so lifeless.
改札の安蛍光灯は
The cheap fluorescent lights at the ticket gates
貴方の影すら落とさない
don't even cast your shadow.
歪んだ無常の遠い日も
The warped, uncertain, distant days
セブンスターの香り
smell of Seven Stars,
味わう如く季節を呼び起こす
and savoring them evoke that season.
あたしが望んだこと自体
The very fact that I expected something
矛盾を優に超えて
goes well beyond contradiction.
一番愛しいあなたの声這い
Your voice is the most dearest of all to me—
掠れさせて居たのだろう
but did I even make that hoarse?
静寂を破るドイツ車とパトカー
German cars and police cars break the silence,
サイレン 爆音
sirens, the sound of explosions,
現実界 或るいは 浮遊
reality, a certain floating.
「不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love my unsettled screams,
未来等見ないで
don't look to the future,
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
live only in the present you can be confident in.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name right,
身体を触って
touch my body;
必要なのは是だけ認めて」
acknowledge that this is the only thing you need."
「不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love my unsettled screams,
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
live only in the present you can be confident in.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name right,
身体を触って
touch my body;
必要なのは是だけ認めて」
acknowledge that this is the only thing you need."
頬を刺す 朝の山手通り
Yamate street in the morning stings my cheeks,
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty box of cigarettes.
今日もまた 足の踏み場はない
Today again I have no space even for my feet,
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
and my small room pampers my loneliness.
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
Yamate Street in the morning stings my cheeks,
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
throwing away an empty pack of cigarettes.
今日もまた足の踏み場はない
Today too, there's nowhere to step;
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
my small room indulges my loneliness.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my restless shrieking,
未来等見ないで
don't look toward a future.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just pile up the present moments I can be sure of,
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
call my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body,
必要なのは是だけ認めて
and acknowledge that this is all I need.
愛している――独り泣き喘いで
I love you... weeping and gasping all alone.
夜道を弄れど虚しい
Fumbling down the night road is so empty.
改札の安蛍光灯は貴方の影すら落とさない
The cheap fluorescent lights of the ticket gate don't even cast your shadow.
Ah、歪んだ無常の遠い日も
Ah, even those warped, fleeting, distant days
セブンスターの香り味わう如く季節を呼び起こす
recall the seasons like tasting the scent of Seven Stars.
あたしが望んだこと自体矛盾を優に超えて
What I wished for goes far beyond mere contradiction;
一番愛していたあなたの声掠れさせて居たのだろう
I must have made the voice of the one I loved most grow hoarse.
静寂を破るドイツ車とパトカー
A German car and a police car break the silence—
サイレン
sirens,
爆音
roaring,
現実界
the real world,
或る浮遊
a certain floating...
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my restless shrieking,
未来等見ないで
don't look toward a future.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just pile up the present moments I can be sure of,
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
call my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body,
必要なのは是だけ認めて
and acknowledge that this is all I need.
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
Yamate Street in the morning stings my cheeks,
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
throwing away an empty pack of cigarettes.
今日もまた足の踏み場はない
Today too, there's nowhere to step;
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
my small room indulges my loneliness.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my restless shrieking,
未来等見ないで
don't look toward a future.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just pile up the present moments I can be sure of,
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
call my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body,
必要なのは是だけ認めて
and acknowledge that this is all I need.
ねえ、あんたわかってない
Hey, you really don't get it.
へらへらのおつむがどうにかなして
Your flippant little head is losing its mind,
うすら寒い言葉ばかりになる
leaving behind only cringeworthy words.
覚えない顔とバイバイできるなら
If I can say goodbye to faces I don't even know,
阿修羅にだってなれるわ
I can turn into Ashura.
裏切られた分だけ墓を掘る
Digging as many graves as I've been betrayed.
逃げるスケスケスケスケ仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape as Buddha!
飛べるステップステップステップ仰せのまま
Fly, step, step, step as you wish!
アンダースタンド アンダースタンド
Understand? Understand?
どーどー閻魔様さえ呑喰って
Devouring even King Enma himself!
騙るスクースクースクー嵐の中
Cheat, sneak, sneak, sneak in a storm!
跳ねるスキップスキップスキップあっそ、へのかっぱ
Prance, skip, skip, skip, oh really, who cares?
アンダースタンド アンダースタンド
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
Might as well bleed them dry to the marrow!
日々の浸みを木々に焼いて暖をとり合う
Burning the oozing titbits of everyday life and basking in its warmth.
義理を誘いだ彼の四肢は散り散りになる
He who defied obligation has his four limbs torn apart.
知りもせずに意味を美意識だと崇る
Finding worth in an aesthetic value without comprehending.
擬似餌じみた弔意に御の字だった
A hilarious full-course meal of pontifications and empty talk.
愉快な御詣のフルコースに
A delightful full-course pilgrimage,
うわべの面をして可愛がった
putting on a superficial face and acting cute.
くだらない圀と踊るくらいなら
If I have to dance with a good-for-nothing country,
悪魔と手繋ぐわ
I'd rather hold the devil's hand.
逃げるスケスケスケスケ仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape as Buddha!
飛べるステップステップステップ仰せのまま
Fly, step, step, step as you wish!
アンダースタンド アンダースタンド
Understand? Understand?
阿鼻地獄の果てまでロックオン
Locking on until the ends of Avici hell!
騙るスクースクースクー嵐の中
Cheat, sneak, sneak, sneak in a storm!
跳ねるスキップスキップスキップあっそ、へのかっぱ
Prance, skip, skip, skip, oh really, who cares?
アンダースタンド アンダースタンド
Understand? Understand?
あんた寝言はあの世で言って
Save your silly talk for the afterlife!
逃げるスケスケスケスケ仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape as Buddha!
飛べるステップステップステップ仰せのまま
Fly, step, step, step as you wish!
アンダースタンド アンダースタンド
Understand? Understand?
どーどー閻魔様さえ呑喰って
Devouring even King Enma himself!
騙るスクースクースクー嵐の中
Cheat, sneak, sneak, sneak in a storm!
跳ねるスキップスキップスキップあっそ、へのかっぱ
Prance, skip, skip, skip, oh really, who cares?
アンダースタンド アンダースタンド
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
Might as well bleed them dry to the marrow!
ねえ、ギャーギャー言っちゃって
Hey, squawking so loudly...
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」っぽいな
Love's spoiler, feels like parting
人生のネタバレ 「死ぬ」っぽいな
Life's spoiler, feels like dying
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
お水飲んでくださいね、すみませんね。
Please drink some water, sorry about that.
あ、私って、すみませんね。
Ah, me... I'm so sorry.
ええと、先ほどはジェンドと罪と罰とアスラちゃんをお届けしました。どうでしたでしょうか？
Uh, earlier I performed "Gendo", "Tsumi to Batsu", and "Asura-chan". How was it?
この後もまだまだライブは続きます！
The live will keep going after this too!
まだ披露してないあんな曲や、こんな曲や、あるかもね！
There might still be songs I haven't performed yet, like this or that!
なのでチャンネルはそのままで、まだ見ててくれたら嬉しいです！
So please keep your channel as is and watch more if you'd like!
ここでみんなにお知らせをさせてください。こちらです！
Please let me make an announcement to everyone here. Here it is!
猪岐リオナ誕生日記念2026のグッズが出ます！やったー！
Isaki Riona's 2026 Birthday Commemorative Merchandise is out! Yay!
では詳細を見ていきましょう。まずは、こちらです！
Now let's look at the details. First, here it is!
リオナオンザステージタペストリー！イラストは明春先生にお描きおろしいただきました。
Riona On The Stage Tapestry! Illustrated by Meiharu-sensei.
ライブ中のリオナをテーマに描かれたイラストで、とっても可愛いイラストになっているので、ぜひ堪能してください！
It features Riona during the live as its theme, and it's super cute, so please enjoy it!
二つ目は、こちら！リオナとおそろいネックレス！
Second is this! Matching necklace with Riona!
真ん中には王冠のデザイン、周りには猪岐リオナのロゴが入っていますので、あの、シンプルになってますのでね、ぜひリオナとおそろいにしてくれたら嬉しいです！
It has a crown design in the middle and Isaki Riona's logo around it. It's nice and simple, so I'd be happy if you matched with Riona!
次は、こちら！リオナのぬいを入れるポーチ！
Next is this! Pouch to put Riona's plushie in!
リオポタ全開のぬいポーチになってます！ぜひね、リオナの、リオナのぬいを入れてくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
It's a plush pouch packed with Rionapotence! I'd be so happy if you put Riona's plushie inside!
ぬい以外に使っても大丈夫だよ、ポーチになるよ。そしてそして、最後は、こちら！
It's totally fine to use it for things other than plushies, it works as a pouch. And last but not least, here it is!
くしゃみ連発ぬいキーホルダー！
Sneezing consecutive plush keychain!
今回描き下ろしイラストの衣装のぬいぐるみキーホルダーになってます。
This is a plush keychain in the outfit from the newly drawn illustration.
なんとね、この手の部分をね、ポチッて押すと、ﾊｰｸｼｮﾝって言うので、いっぱい押してね、いっぱい浴びてもらえればと思います！
And you know, if you press this hand part, it goes "Achoo!", so I hope you press it a lot and bathe in it!
そして改めてね、フルセットの方全部見ていきましょう。こちら！
And let's look through the full set again. Here!
ま、リラックス！もちろん、フルセット購入特典もあります！こちら！
Relax! Of course, there are also full set purchase bonuses! Here!
フルセット購入特典の1つ目は、直筆サインと箔押しメッセージ入りのバックステージパス風カードです！
The first full set purchase bonus is a backstage pass-style card with an autograph and foil-stamped message!
こちらも明春先生のイラストにすべて私から1つ1つﾊﾝﾊﾝﾊﾝﾊﾝﾊﾝﾊﾝﾃってサインさせていただくので、よかったらぜひ買ってみてください！
For this as well, I'll personally sign every single one over Meiharu-sensei's illustration, so please consider buying it!
二つ目は特典ボイス「ライブ前に君と」です！
The second is the bonus voice "With You Before the Live"!
ライブ前にね、こう緊張してね、へへへってなっているリオナを励ますシチュエーションとなっております！
It's a situation where you encourage Riona who is all nervous and going "hehee" before the live!
こちらのグッズは21時9時からカートオープンです！みんなよかったらぜ、ぜひ、ゲットしてください！
These goods open in the cart at 9:00 PM! Everyone, please go ahead and get them!
そして大事なお知らせが二つ目、あります。聞いてください。
And there is a second important announcement. Please listen.
猪岐リオナの初ソロの新曲がでます！やったー！タイトルは「Ring my name」です！
Isaki Riona's first solo new song is coming out! Yay! The title is "Ring my name"!
こちら、私の思い出だったり、これから先どうやってこう進んでいくか、私は進んでいくぞ、というおしゃれで、洋楽に、洋楽風に表現された曲となっております。
This song is expressed in a stylish, Western-music style about my memories and how I will keep moving forward from here on out.
こちらセクシーな振り付けもついているので、よかったらそこに注目もしてくださると嬉しいです！
It also comes with sexy choreography, so I'd be happy if you paid attention to that as well!
この後このライブが終わった後すぐにMVも公開されますし、
Right after this live ends, the MV will also be released,
この後24時からデジタルリリースもあるので、ぜひいっぱい聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
and there's a digital release starting at midnight, so I hope you'll listen to it a lot!
やっぱりこの後は新曲やっちゃいますよね！
Of course, after this we're doing the new song, right?
ということでね、まあやっていくんですけど、その前のにちょっと語ってくださいよ。
So with that said, we're going to do it, but let me talk a bit before that.
まあね、リオナはね、まだまだなことがいっぱいあって、かなえたい夢もいっぱいあります。
Well, you know, Riona still has so many things to achieve and so many dreams she wants to fulfill.
なのは、まだまだ何も手にしてない私かもしれないけど、一緒に付いて来てくれたあなたと一緒にいろんな夢だったり思い出を作っていきたいです！
So even though I might still be someone who hasn't achieved anything yet, I want to create various dreams and memories together with you who followed along with me!
絶対後悔はさせないので、これからも私に付いて来てくれると嬉しいです！よろしくお願いします！
I definitely won't let you regret it, so I'd be happy if you kept following me! Thank you very much!
そしてこの後は、え、新曲の披露の前に、ホロライブの先輩方の折り曲を使ったダンスメドレーをお届けします！こちらたくさんのジャンルのダンスを踊る
And after this, uh, before premiering the new song, we'll deliver a dance medley using Hololive seniors' folded tracks! Dancing to many genres of dance...
ので
So let's get started,
ぜひ見てください！
please be sure to watch!
行くよ、心の準備できた？
Here we go, I've got my heart ready!
ミュージック、
Music,
スタート！
start!
失礼しますが、RIP♡
Excuse my rudeness, but could you please RIP?
Ah, listen up, yeah
I'm a Reaper, so I'm not a god
But I'm here to say that I'm the one who's in charge
Don't be a fool, I'm the one who's in charge
(Yeah, I'm the one who's in charge)
式神ぜぜか、ライオナ！
Shikigami sezeka, Riona!
素敵な朝さ 私を奪って
Sukina Asan sa watashi wo ubate
Velvet shadows call my name
微熱は隠して 午前零時
Binetsu wa kakushite gozen reiji
今更 Veilがほどけ
Imasara Veil ga hodo ke
I'm breaking into the night
まだ夜は醒めやしない
Mada yoru wa samete yanai
Doggy doggy god's street
Listen up, yeah
壱弐参飛んで八十し
Ichi-ni-san-shi tobide hasshi
楽しがらせばいいじゃない
Tanoshi garaseba ii janai
勝手チャッパでチコ段はじけて壊れちゃお
Katsu te chappa de chiko dan hajikete kowarechao
この先は地獄だ世界は地獄だ dancing day
Kono saki wa jigoku da sekai wa jigoku da dancing day
勝手チャッパでチコ段はじけて壊れちゃお
Katsu te chappa de chiko dan hajikete kowarechao
この先は地獄だ世界は地獄だ dancing day
Kono saki wa jigoku da sekai wa jigoku da dancing day
ずっと夢見ていることかもしれない
Zutto yume miteru koto kamo shirenai
この世界はすべてクソみたいな趣味ね
Kono sekai wa subete kuso mitai na shumi ne
天使も悪魔もいないバラ色の世界へ
Tenshi mo akuma mo inai barairo no sekai e
Contas hale'ilia on Shallys
Animita potima i ji'ulyc
つまらないデイズもう散々ね！
Boring days, already had enough!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
A life just wishing for miracles
Watch me do-do-do-do-do
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Magic without any secret tricks
つまらないデイズもう散々ね！
Boring days, already had enough!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
A life just wishing for miracles
Watch me do-do-do-do-do
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Magic without any secret tricks
Bibbidi-babbidi-boo, 見せてYour Smile!
Bibbidi-babbidi-boo, show me your smile!
扉を開け放て新世界へ！
Let's open up the door to a new world!
Bibbidi-babbidi-boo, 見せてYour Smile!
Bibbidi-babbidi-boo, show me your smile!
扉を開け放て新世界へ！
Let's open up the door to a new world!
Ring my name
I'm dressed in lace
甘い嘘は act
Sweet lies are act
囁くの 「Want more?」
Whispering 'Want more?'
吐息まで danger
Until the sigh, danger
Every step I take
心ごと奪って
Stealing your heart away
Velvet shadows call my name
微熱は隠して
Hiding a slight fever
午前零時
Midnight
今 Veilがほどけ
Now the veil is undone
I'm breaking into the night
まだ夜は醒めやしない
The night still won't wake up
さあ、誰も彼も焦がれるままで
Until everyone burns out and goes mad
私を見て...
Look at me...
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, let it echo out
今から What's my life?
Now from here, what's my life?
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now, let it flourish
煌めく Reina
Shimmering Reina
指先まで優雅に揺れる
Dancing with elegance down to my fingertips
鏡越しの操り人形
A marionette behind the mirror
壊れそうに微笑んで
Smiling as if I'm about to break
瞳の奥 Falling low
Deep in the eyes, falling low
唇まで Like a ghost I can't stop
Like a ghost, I can't stop
巡る走馬灯さ 魅せましょう
Wandering through all these mazes, let's show them!
綺麗な嘘で
With a pretty lie
飾らないの Masquerade
A masquerade with nothing to adorn it
どんでんスキップ ジプロメテウス
Go ahead, skip it, G-prometheus
それならばいっそ Shall we dance?
If that's the case, then shall we dance?
Flavor like a little tease
今さら Bad、マーク、連打、Bot、Bot
Now, it's just bad, mark, spam, repeat, bot, bot
やってられねーな
I'm so sick of this!
I'm a wonder, can't look away
魅せつけるの 全てを賭けて
Risking it all to captivate you
Click, click, tap, tap, and keep on posing
Flick, flick, snap, snap, and everybody dancing
I'm dressed in lace
甘い嘘は act
Sweet lies are act
囁くの「want more?」
Whispering "want more?"
吐息まで danger
Even my sigh is danger
every step i take
心ごと奪って
Stealing my heart
velvet shadows call my name
微熱の中
In a slight fever
景色が溶けて
The scenery melts
まだ夢は覚めない
The dream hasn't woken up yet
To younger me, "you're alright"
名もなきあの頃に
In those nameless days
「後悔はない」
"No regrets"
Ring my name 響かせるわ
I'll make ring my name resonate
今から watch me rise
Now watch me rise
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now, if I bloom in glory
煌めく reina
Glittering reina
明け方まで気高く踊る 琥珀色の仮面舞踏会
Dancing proudly until dawn, amber masquerade
壊れそうに舞い乱れ
Dancing wildly as if I'm going to break
Viva la reina cantad al alba ya
Ring my name 響かせるわ 今から watch me rise
I'll make ring my name resonate, now watch me rise
泡沫のtiaraに
To the ephemeral tiara
魅せられ ただ憧れ
Enchanted, just longing
手を伸ばして
Reaching out my hand
これからも私についてきてください！
Please continue to follow me!
以上、響咲リオナでした！
That's all, I'm Yukisaki Riona!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
響咲リオナ生誕祭 2026 お越しいただき、ありがとうございました！！
Yukisaki Riona Birthday Festival 2026. Thank you so much for coming!!
これからも皆さんと一緒に居たい 貴方の居場所でありたい！！
I want to keep being with you all, and be your safe place!!
お届けしたパフォーマンスが貴方の心に少しでも何かを残せているといいな
I hope my performance left something in your heart, even just a little.
本当に本当にありがとう！！ 響咲リオナでした。
Thank you so very much!! This was Yukisaki Riona.